Guide to the Werner Pfeiffer Collection, 1953-2017
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- 5000 PAINTINGS
  - 5002: Shaped, Dimensional and Rotating Paintings – Drawings and Sketches
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—018)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—019)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—020)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (11 x 8.5) (5002—021)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—022)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—023)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—024)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—025)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—026)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—027)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-13; (8.5 x 11) (5002—028)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-13; (8.5 x 11) (5002—029)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-13; (8.5 x 11) (5002—030)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-13; (8.5 x 11) (5002—031)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-13; (8.5 x 11) (5002—032)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11) (5002—033)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—034)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—035)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—036)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—037)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—038)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—039)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—040)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-14; (8.5 x 11) (5002—041)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-15; (8.5 x 11) (5002—042)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-15; (8.5 x 11) (5002—043)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-15; (8.5 x 11) (5002—044)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-15; (8.5 x 11) (5002—045)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-15; (11 x 8.5) (5002—046)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—047)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—048)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (11 x 8.5) (5002—049)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—050)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—051)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—052)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—053)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-17; (8.5 x 11) (5002—054)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—055)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—056)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002 –057)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—058)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—059)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—060)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—061)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—062)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—063)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—064)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—065)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-18; (8.5 x 11) (5002—066)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-20; (8.5 x 11) (5002—067)
    - Maquette for Catalogue including 18 sketches in color pencil and 6 sketches in black and white, 1977-03; (9 x 8.5) (5002—068)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01-23; (8.5 x 11) (5002—069)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01-23; (8.5 x 11) (5002—070)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01; (9 x 8.5) (5002—071)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5002—072)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5002—073)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01-13; (11 x 8.5) (5002—074)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01-13; (11 x 8.5) (5002—075)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1978-01-13; (8.5 x 11) (5002—076)
    - Maquette – left side, 1978-01; (11 x 6) (5002—077)
    - Maquette – center, 1978-01; (11 x 6) (5002—078)
    - Maquette – center, 1978-01; (11 x 6) (5002—079)
    - Maquette – right side, 1978-01; (11 x 6) (5002—080)
    - 16 Studies...., 1976-09; (8.5 x 10) (5002—081)
    - Shaped Canvas, untitled, 1979; (31 x 32) (5002—082)
    - Shaped Canvas, untitled, 1979; (29 x 30) (5002—083)
  - 5003: System Kunst, Systems Art, Sectional Works, Zippers — Drawings, Sketches, Maquettes
    - Collage, pencil drawing, 1977-04-07; (4.5 x 7) (5003—001)
    - Collage, pencil drawing, 1977-04-08; (4 x 7) (5003—002)
    - Collage, pencil drawing, 1977-04-11; (4.25 x 8) (5003—003)
    - Collage, pencil drawing, 1977-04-11; (4 x 6.5) (5003—004)
    - Collage, pencil drawing, 1977-04-11; (3.75 x 6.5) (5003—005)
    - Black and white pencil sketch, 1977-04-16; (10.5 x 13) (5003—006)
    - Black and white ballpoint pen sketch, 1977-04-16; (10.5 x 13) (5003—007)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-05; (4.25 x 4 25) (5003—008)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-05; (4 x 4) (5003—009)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (9.5 x 7) (5003—010)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (3.5 x 9.5) (5003—011)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (8.25 x 7) (5003—012)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (9.5 x 1.25) (5003—013)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (4.75 x 6) (5003—014)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (9 x 7) (5003—015)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (4.75 x 4.75) (5003—016)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-07; (9.5 x 6) (5003—017)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-13; (4.75 x 4.75) (5003—018)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-13; (9.5 x 7) (5003—019)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-13; (4.5 x 7) (5003—020)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-13; (4.25 x 7) (5003—021)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-06-13; (5 x 7.5) (5003—022)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-10-14; (3.5 x 3.5) (5003—023)
    - Black and white pencil drawing, 1977-10-14; (2 x 5) (5003—024)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-11; (7.75 x 13.25) (5003—025)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1977-11; (7.75 x 13.25) (5003—026)
    - Color pencil drawing on tissue, 1978-10; (10.5 x 3.25) (5003—027)
    - Color pencil on graph paper, 1978-10; (10.25 x 2.5) (5003—028)
    - Color pencil on graph paper, 1978-10; (10.25 x 5.5) (5003—029)
    - Color pencil drawing, 1980-02; (11.5 x 6) (5003—030)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1979-05; (8.5 x 7.5) (5003—031)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1979-05; (10.5 x 7.75) (5003—032)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1979-05; (10 x 7.75) (5003—033)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1979-11; (8.75 x 6) (5003—034)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1979-11; (9 x 7) (5003—035)
    - Collage, color pencil drawing, 1979-11; (8.75 x 6) (5003—036)
    - Collage, acrylic, pencil, 3 parts, 1979-11; (14.5 x 6) (5003—037)
    - Maquette with zipper, 1980-01; (8.5 x 10.5) (5003—038)
    - Maquette, paper, 1980-02; (13 x 4) (5003—039)
    - Maquette, paper, 1997-05; (9 x 4.5) (5003—040)
    - Zipper Painting no. 21 panels, 1990; (17 x 11) (5003—041)
    - Zipper Painting no. 22 panels, 1994; (17 x 11) (5003—042)
    - Sectional Painting collage sketch, 1978-01; (8 x 8) (5003—043)
    - Model for 'Orion,' board, 1978-01; (5 x 5) (5003—044)
    - Black and white pencil sketches, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5003—045)
    - Black and white pencil sketches, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5003—046)
    - Color pencil sketch, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5003—047)
    - Venus – color pencil sketch, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5003—048)
    - Color pencil sketch, 1978-01; (8.5 x 11) (5003—049)
    - Sketch for Delta Series, 1978-01; (9.5 x 8.5) (5003—050)
    - Collage,color pencil drawing, 1977-07; (16.75 x 10) (5003—051)
    - Collage, color pencil, 1977-06; (8.5 x 11) (5003—052)
    - Collage, color pencil, 1979-05; (11 x 7.75) (5003—053)
    - Collage, color pencil, 1979-05; (11 x 7.75) (5003—054)
    - Collage, color pencil, 1979-05; (11 x 7.75) (5003—055)
    - Study for book without words, 1965; (17 x 17) (5003—056)
    - Pluto – study for sectional print, 1973; (30 x 24) (5003 –057)
    - Study for sectionl painting, 1974; (various) (5003—058)
    - Documentation for 'Jupiter', 1976; (19.5 x 14) (5003—059)
    - Documentation for Zipper Painting no. 3, 1977; (14.5 x 11.5) (5003—060)
    - Documantation for 'Venus', 1978; (14.5 x 11.5) (5003—061)
    - Docu. of Zipper no. 9, 4 sheets, 1978; (20 x 28 each) (5003—062)
    - Sectional Watercalor, 12 parts, 1978; (33 x 24) (5003—063)
    - 'Blue Hues', study, 5 parts, 1978; (various) (5003—064)
    - 'Yellow Hues', study, 5 parts, 1978; (various) (5003—065)
    - Study for wall painting, 1988; (various) (5003—066)
    - Zipper Paintings, brochure, 2008; (8.5 x 8.5) (5003—067)
- 6000 COLLAGES
  - 6001: Collage Constructions
    - Rhythmic no. 1 – lettice like collage, 1979; (30 x 20) (6001—001)
    - Rhythmic no. 2 – lettice like collage, 1979; (28 x 18) (6001—002)
    - Rhythmic no. 6 – lettice like collage, 1980; (30 x 22) (6001—003)
    - Rhythmic no. 7 – lettice like collage, 1980; (34 x 22) (6001—004)
    - Rhythmic no. 8 – lettice like collage, 1980; (22 x 30) (6001—005)
    - Rhythmic no. 10 – lettice like collage, 1980; (32 x 22) (6001—006)
    - Rhythmic no. 11 – lettice like collage, 1980; (23 x 31) (6001—007)
    - Rhythmic no. 12 – lettice like collage, 1980; (32 x 21) (6001—008)
    - Rhythmic no. 13 – lettice like collage, 1980; (34 x 24) (6001—009)
  - 6002: Collages
    - Collage, 2003-01-01; (10 x 10) (6002—001)
    - Collage, 2003-01-02; (10 x 10) (6002—002)
    - Collage, 2003-01-03; (10 x 10) (6002—003)
    - Collage, 2003-01-02; (10 x 10) (6002—004)
    - Collage, 2003-01-07; (10 x 10) (6002—005)
    - Collage, 2003-01-09; (10 x 10) (6002—006)
    - Collage, 2003-01-10; (10 x 10) (6002—007)
    - Collage, 2003-01-11; (10 x 10) (6002—008)
    - Collage, 2003-01-12; (10 x 10) (6002—009)
    - Collage, 2003-01-13; (10 x 10) (6002—010)
    - Collage, 2003-01-14; (10 x 10) (6002—011)
    - Collage, 2003-01-15; (10 x 10) (6002—012)
    - Collage, 2003-01-16; (10 x 10) (6002—013)
    - Collage, 2003-01-17; (10 x 10) (6002—014)
    - Collage, 2003-01-18; (10 x 10) (6002—015)
    - Collage, 2003-01-19; (10 x 10) (6002—016)
    - Collage, 2003-01-20; (10 x 10) (6002—017)
    - Collage, 2003-01-21; (10 x 10) (6002—018)
    - Collage, 2003-01-22; (10 x 10) (6002—019)
    - Collage, 2003-01-23; (10 x 10) (6002—020)
    - Collage, 2003-01-25; (10 x 10) (6002—021)
    - Collage, 2003-01-26; (10 x 10) (6002—022)
    - Collage, 2003-01-29; (10 x 10) (6002—023)
    - Collage, 2003-01-30; (10 x 10) (6002—024)
    - Collage, 2003-01-31; (10 x 10) (6002—025)
    - Collage, 2003-02-04; (10 x 10) (6002—026)
    - Collage, 2003-02-05; (10 x 10) (6002—027)
    - Collage, 2003-02-07; (10 x 10) (6002—028)
    - Collage, 2003-02-10; (10 x 10) (6002—029)
    - Collage, 2003-02-11; (10 x 10) (6002—030)
    - Collage, 2003-02-12; (10 x 10) (6002—031)
    - Collage, 2003-02-13; (10 x 10) (6002—032)
    - Collage, 2003-02-14; (10 x 10) (6002—033)
    - Collage, 2003-02-15; (10 x 10) (6002—034)
    - Collage, 2003-02-16; (10 x 10) (6002—035)
    - Collage, 2003-02-17; (10 x 10) (6002—036)
    - Collage, 2003-02-18; (10 x 10) (6002—037)
    - Collage, 2003-02-19; (10 x 10) (6002—038)
    - Collage, 2003-02-20; (10 x 10) (6002—039)
    - Collage, 2003-02-21; (10 x 10) (6002—040)
    - Collage, 2003-02-22; (10 x 10) (6002—041)
    - Collage, 2003-02-23; (10 x 10) (6002—042)
    - Collage, 2003-02-24; (10 x 10) (6002—043)
    - Collage, 2003-02-25; (10 x 10) (6002—044)
    - Collage, 2003-02-27; (10 x 10) (6002—045)
    - Collage, 2003-02-28; (10 x 10) (6002—046)
    - Collage, 2003-03-01; (10 x 10) (6002—047)
    - Collage, 2003-03-02; (10 x 10) (6002—048)
    - Collage, 2003-03-03; (10 x 10) (6002—049)
    - Collage, 2003-03-04; (10 x 10) (6002—050)
    - Collage, 2003-03-05; (10 x 10) (6002—051)
    - Collage, 2003-03-06; (10 x 10) (6002—052)
    - Collage, 2003-03-08; (10 x 10) (6002—053)
    - Collage, 2003-03-09; (10 x 10) (6002—054)
    - Collage, 2003-03-10; (10 x 10) (6002—055)
    - Collage, 2003-03-11; (10 x 10) (6002—056)
    - Collage, 2003-03-12; (10 x 10) (6002 –057)
    - Collage, 2003-03-13; (10 x 10) (6002—058)
    - Collage, 2003-03-14; (10 x 10) (6002—059)
    - Collage, 2003-03-15; (10 x 10) (6002—060)
- 7000 BOOKS
  - 7005: Experimental Pieces - one of a kind
    - Frog Book – letterpress, 1995; (5.25 x 5.5 x 3) (7005—001)
    - Scroll in small Wooden Box – written text, sewn together, 1995; (3 dia. X 1.75) (7005—002)
    - Open Book with Heart – book, 3 d. heart covered in type, 1996; (11.25 x 7.5 x 2) (7005—003)
    - "Poirier" Vintage – cut glass bottle with 8' scroll, 1996; (12.5 x 3.25 dia.) (7005—004)
    - "The Picnic" - book – 16 cut pages, marbleized inserts, 1996; (9 x 8.75 x 0.5) (7005—005)
    - Paper-Machế Heart Book – sculpted covers, type ribbons, 1997; (3.5 x 3.5 x 3.5) (7005—006)
    - Blind – blind with text, 4' fully extended, 1997; (6 x 1.5 x 0.5) (7005—007)
    - Your 50th – 50 envelopes on metal post, 1997; (6.5 x 9.75 x 1.75) (7005—008)
    - Happy Valentines – hearts, text ribbons in clam shell, 1998; (6.75 x 9.5 x 1.5) (7005—009)
    - Box with 4 letter dices, lens – rolled up ribbons in shape of 51, 1998; (5.25 x 6.5 x 2.5) (7005—010)
    - Pencil Book – 32 pencils for holes in cover, 1999; (7.5 x 8.5 x 1.25) (7005—011)
    - Collage Book with threads – accordion fold, 36" fully extendended, 1999; (2.5 x 8.25 x 1.25) (7005—012)
    - No. 53 Book - Wood Type Cover – small book, with type ribbons, 2000; (2.5 x 3.5 x 2) (7005—013)
    - Shaped Book – 1 side open, 3d message inside, 2001; (4 x 4 x 4) (7005—014)
    - Jack in the Box – diamond fold with text, 2001; (4.5 x 4.5 x 2) (7005—015)
    - Heart in Circle – type ribbons in shape of heart, 2002; (3.25 x 3.25 x 2) (7005—016)
    - Happy Birthday – box with 25 small books inside, 2002; (7 x 7 x 0.5) (7005—017)
    - Wind-Up Scroll – 4' text ribbon and wind-up mechanism., 2003; (4 x 3.5 x 2.25) (7005—018)
    - Love 56 – embossed cover – fold-out sheets of photographs, 2003; (5.5 x 5.75 x 0.5) (7005—019)
    - Circular Spindle in Box – small scrolls attached to spindle, 2004; (3.5 x 3.5 x 2.5) (7005—020)
    - Stone Book – small book bound by rocks, 2004; (3.5 x 4 x 2.5) (7005—021)
    - Marguerite – book in shape of strainer, heart, 2005; (4.5 dia. X 2.5) (7005—022)
    - You Can't See it – Fan Book – book with heart and hidden text, 2006; (6.5 x 12.5 x 1.25) (7005—023)
    - Stick Book – 16 sticks with words, 2007; (3.75 x 3.75 x 3.5) (7005—024)
    - Flip Book – flip book with 2 messages, 2008; (4.5 x 2.5 x .75) (7005—025)
    - Happy 63rd Birthday – double accordion book, 2009; (4.25 x 4.5 x 0.5) (7005—026)
    - Heart Sculpture – paper hearts on pedestal, 2010; (4.25 x 4.25 x 6) (7005—027)
    - Prayer Mill – zig-zag fold on wooden handle, 2010; (6.5 dia. X 7.5) (7005—028)
    - Split Heart – multiple small hearts on wire, 2011; (4.25 x 4.25 x 5.5) (7005—029)
    - Adjustable Message – turing columns with messages, 2011; (9.5 x 3 x 0.5) (7005—030)
    - Plexi Box – ribbons of text in plexi box, 2012; (3.75 x 3.75 x 3.75) (7005—031)
    - Open/Close – diamond shapes with messages, 2013; (4 x 6 x 1.25) (7005—032)
    - Poems and Hearts – watercolor, text, wooden covers, 2014; (1.5 x 5.5 x 1.25) (7005—033)
    - 16' of Happiness – written text on tape measure, 2014; (3.5 x 3.5 x 2.25) (7005—034)
    - Sphere – sphere of circular shapes, text, 2015; (4.5 dia.) (7005—035)
    - Watchful Eye – play on exchangeable letters, 2016; (2.5 x 4 x 0.5) (7005—036)
    - Double Continuum – double sided text ribbon, 2016; (6 x 6 x 0.5) (7005—037)
    - Puzzle – two-sided piece in plastic panel, 2017; (6.25 x 7 x 1.25) (7005—038)
    - Hands On – adjustable game, 10 panels, 2017; (4.25 x 4.25 x 1.5) (7005—039)
    - Greeting card – covers with pinholes over text bloc, 1995-08; (8 x 5.25) (7005—040—01)
    - Greeting card – "Soul Echoes" - embossed lines and shapes, 1995-09-02; (5 x 7) (7005—040—02)
    - Greeting card – sprayed circle, dripping paint, eyelet, 1995-10-04; (7 x 5) (7005—040—03)
    - Greeting card – booklet format with eyelets and red woolen thread, 1995-11-29; (5.5 x 8.75) (7005—040—04)
    - Greeting card – marbleized paper, red thread, embossments, 1996-07; (4.5 x 4.5) (7005—040—05)
    - Greeting card – small collage, embossments, cut-out hearts, 1996-10; (2.75 x 3.75) (7005—040—06)
    - Greeting card – image of my ear, embossments, 1997-05; (3.25 x 4.25) (7005—040—07)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossments, red thread, 1997-08; (3.25 x 4.25) (7005—040—08)
    - Greeting card – collage, threads, embossments, needle-pricks, 1998-05; (5.5 x 8.5) (7005—040—09)
    - Greeting card – collage, thread and needle-prick,s, 1999-05; (5.75 x 8.25) (7005—040—10)
    - Greeting card – needle-pricks, red thread, small beats, 2000-02-14; (5.75 x 8.5) (7005—040—11)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossment, thread, 2000-05; (5.5 x 8) (7005—040—12)
    - Greeting card – collage plus embossments, 2001-05; (5.75 x 7.25) (7005—040—13)
    - Greeting card – collage plus embossments, 2002-05; (5 x 8) (7005—040—14)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossments, threads, 2003-05; (5.5 x 8.5) (7005—040—15)
    - Greeting card – collage plus embossments, 2004-05; (9 x 9) (7005—040—16)
    - Greeting card – collage, watercolor, embossments, needle-pricks, 2005-02; (6 x 8.75) (7005—040—17)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossments, red thread, 2005-05; (6.25 x 6.25) (7005—040—18)
    - Greeting card – collage plus embossments, 2006-05; (7.5 x 10) (7005—040—19)
    - Greeting card – collage plus embossment, gauze, 2008-05; (7 x 8.5) (7005—040—20)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossments, drawing, 2010-05; (5.25 x 8) (7005—040—21)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossments, drawing, 2011-05; (6.75 x 8) (7005—040—22)
    - Greeting card – collage, gauze, embossment, 2012-02; (6 x 8) (7005—040—23)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossment, drawing, 2013-05; (5.5 x 8.25) (7005—040—24)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossment, drawing, 2014-05; (5.5 x 7) (7005—040—25)
    - Greeting card – adjustable heart and text, drawings, 2015-02; (8 x 8) (7005—040—26)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossment, drawing, 2015-05; (6.25 x 6.5) (7005—040—27)
    - Greeting card – collage, embossment, red thread with heart, 2016-05; (5.5 x 8) (7005—040—28)
    - Greeting card – collage, drawing, embossment, 2017-02; (5.75 x 7.5) (7005—040—29)
    - Greeting card – collage, drawing, embossment, 2017-05; (7.5 x 8.5) (7005—040—30)
- 8000 PUBLICITY and RECORDS
  - 8001: Visual Diaries
    - 1963-1975 (8001—001)
    - 1975-1979 (8001—002)
    - 1980-1984 (8001—003)
    - 1984-1987 (8001—004)
    - 1987-1991 (8001—005)
    - 1992-1994 (8001—006)
    - 1995-2006 (8001—007)
    - 2007-2015 (8001—008)
  - 8002: Catalogues, Announcements and Publications
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Prints, Self-published, 1971 (8002—001)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Dimensionale Objekte, Galerie der Stadt Stuttgart, 1980 (8002—002)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Dimensional Prints, Flat Rock Press, 1983 (8002—003)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – White Shadow Series, Neville Sargent Gallery, 1987 (8002—004)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Color Echoes, Shippee Gallery, 1987 (8002—005)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Endangered Species, Weimar, 1993 (8002—006)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Endangered Species, Cantz Verlag, 1994 (8002—007)
    - Buchobjekte – W. Pfeiffer, L. Poirier, Württembergische Landesbibliothek, 2001 (8002—008)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Censor, Villain...., Smith, PEN, Cornell, University of Toronto, 2008 (8002—009)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Re-examining Books, Vassar College, 2012 (8002—010)
    - Werner Pfeiffer – Are Books Obsolete, Bucknell, Lafayette, 2016 (8002—011)
    - Announcements
    - Pratt Gallery, Brooklyn, New York – Liber Mobile Exhibit, 1968 (8002—012)
    - Young and Rubicam Gallery, New York – Liber Mobile Exhibit, 1968 (8002—013)
    - Knauer Expo, Stuttgart – Liber Mobile Exhibit, 1969 (8002—014)
    - AAA Gallery, New York – New Talent in Printmaking, 1971 (8002—015)
    - AAA Gallery, New York – Brochure, 1971 (8002—016)
    - AAA Gallery, New York – International Collection, 1971 (8002—017)
    - Galerie Interior, Frankfurt – Prints, 1972 (8002—018)
    - Philippine Cultural Centers – Contemp. American Prints, 1972 (8002—019)
    - Hong Kong City Museum – Graphics Now – USA, 1972 (8002—020)
    - Cultural Center, Tel Aviv – 40 New American Prints, 1973 (8002—021)
    - Yugoslavia and Rumania – American Graphics, 1973 (8002—022)
    - Galerie Mearklin, Stuttgart – Zeichnungen and Grafik, 1974 (8002—023)
    - International Associated Artists, Miami – Werner Pfeiffer, Prints, 1974 (8002—024)
    - The Gallery at West Cornwall – Graphics and Painting, 1974 (8002—025)
    - The Print Cabinet, Redding – Abstract Prints, 1974 (8002—026)
    - RIT Gallery, Rochester – Modern Printmakers, 1974 (8002—027)
    - Silvermine Gallery – 10th National Print Exhibit, 1974 (8002—028)
    - Studio, House Tour Cornwall and Litchfield – Announcement, 1974 (8002—029)
    - Linköping Museum, Sweden – Prints and Drawings, 1974 (8002—030)
    - Linköping Museum – Brochure, 1974 (8002—031)
    - Jorgensen Gallery at University of Connecticut – Graphics and Design, 1975 (8002—032)
    - Jorgensen Gallery at University of Connecticut – Brochure, 1975 (8002—033)
    - Galeri Grafikhuset, Stockholm – Prints and Drawings, 1975 (8002—034)
    - SCAF Gallery, Sharon, Connecticut – Graphics, Painting, Photography, 1975 (8002—035)
    - SCAF Gallery – Brochure, 1975 (8002—036)
    - Galleriet, Lund, 1975 (8002—037)
    - Bethel Gallery, Bethel, Connecticut, 1977 (8002—038)
    - Bibi Nelson, La Napoule – Prints, Drawings, Collages, 1978 (8002—039)
    - Galerie Roger, Nice – Prints, Drawings, Collages, 1979 (8002—040)
    - Galerie Roger, Nice – 2nd Announcement, 1979 (8002—041)
    - Galleri Gränden, Sweden – Prints, 1979 (8002—042)
    - The Deck, Cornwall, Connecticut – The last Picture Show, 1979 (8002—043)
    - Galerie der Stadt Stuttgart – Dimensionale Objekte, 1980 (8002—044)
    - Bernstrom, London, 1980 (8002—045)
    - Rye Art Center, 1980 (8002—046)
    - Post Card, 1980 (8002—047)
    - Post Card, 1980 (8002—048)
    - Post Card, 1980 (8002—049)
    - Post Card, 1980 (8002—050)
    - Post Card, 1980 (8002—051)
    - Post Card, 1980 (8002—052)
    - The Silo Gallery, New Milford, 1980 (8002—053)
    - Galerie Brusberg, Hannover – Dimensional Prints, 1980 (8002—054)
    - Szoke Gallery, New York – Paperworks, 1981 (8002—055)
    - Mattatuck Museum, Waterbury, 1981 (8002—056)
    - The Silo Gallery, New Milford, 1982 (8002—057)
    - Cardonsky Gallery, Kent, 1982 (8002—058)
    - Gallery of Graphic Arts, New York – Dimensional Prints, 1982 (8002—059)
    - Washington Art Association – Dimensional Prints, Sculpture, 1983 (8002—060)
    - Pelham Art Center – Prints and Drawings, 1983 (8002—061)
    - Neville-Sargent Gallery, Chicago, 1983 (8002—062)
    - The Norfolk Library – Book Objects, 1984 (8002—063)
    - Fame Gallery, Houston – Dimensional Prints, 1984 (8002—064)
    - Atria Gallery, Hartford – Dimensional Prints, 1984 (8002—065)
    - Atria Gallery, Hartford – Brochure, 1984 (8002—066)
    - Image South Gallery, Atlanta – Paperworks, 1984 (8002—067)
    - Jos. Smith Gallery, New Haven – Dimensional Prints, 1984 (8002—068)
    - Cornwall Gallery – Graphics, 1984 (8002—069)
    - Mattatuck Museum, 1984 (8002—070)
    - Pratt Galleries – Faculty Exhibit, 1985 (8002—071)
    - Silvermine Gallery – Prints, 1985 (8002—072)
    - Old Lyme Art Works – Connecticut Prints, 1985 (8002—073)
    - Wilson Gallery – Neville-Sargent Artists, 1985 (8002—074)
    - College Board Collection, 1985 (8002—075)